[{"question": " okay rach, that muffin and espresso, $4.50. ross, double latte, $2.75. chandler, coffee and a scone, $4.25. and pheebs, herbal tea, $1.25. so, all together that&#146;s  $12.75.", "answer": " this coming from the man who couldn&#146;t split our 80 dollar phone bill in half.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " how much do i owe you for the muffin and the latte?", "answer": " oh that&#146;s on the house courtesy of joey tribbiani.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " oh great! well, tell him thanks. and since uh, joey seems like such a nice guy, maybe we could go on a date sometime?", "answer": " well, he&#146;s not used to women being so forward with him; but uh, i good check with him&#151;he says it&#146;s okay.  great! thanks! bye-bye!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " hey joey, how come our stuff isn&#146;t free?", "answer": " it will be when you look like that in a tight skirt! this is great! i&#146;m getting more dates than ever!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " wait a minute, you&#146;re only giving free stuff away to the pretty girls?", "answer": " yeah joey that is so gross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " how about a scone on the house baby?", "answer": "  i&#146;m pretty.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " hey does anyone have any gum?", "answer": " oh i do!  oh, y&#146;know what? no.  wait a second.  i know it&#146;s in here somewhere.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " y&#146;know what? i&#146;m good! i&#146;m good!", "answer": "  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey, what are you doing here? shouldn&#146;t you be at work?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": "  ugh, they sent me home. they said i can&#146;t work if i&#146;m sick.", "answer": " ohh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " i&#146;m so sorry you&#146;re sick.", "answer": " i&#146;m not sick!! i don&#146;t get sick! getting sick is for weaklings and for pansies!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " i&#146;m gonna grab you some tissue.", "answer": " i don&#146;t need a tissue! i&#146;m fine-d!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " when you put a &#145;d&#146; at the end of &#145;fine&#146; you&#146;re not fine.", "answer": " i&#146;m fine-d. i&#146;m fine-d! y&#146;know, it&#146;s a really hard word to say.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " hi, is rachel here? i&#146;m her sister.", "answer": " oh my god, jill!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " oh my god, introduce us!", "answer": " this is chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " and you know monica and ross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " hi jill.", "answer": " and that&#146;s phoebe , and that&#146;s joey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " hey,  how you doin&#146;?", "answer": " don&#146;t!!   honey, what are you doing here?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": "  which-which sister is this? is this the spoiled one or that&#146;s bitter?", "answer": "  daddy cut me off.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " never mind, i got it.", "answer": " and y&#146;know what i said to him? &quot;i&#146;m gonna hire a lawyer and i&#146;m gonna sue you and take all your money. then i&#146;m gonna cut you off!&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " wow! what did he say?", "answer": " that he wouldn&#146;t pay for my lawyer! then he told me to come here and learn about the value of money from the one daughter he&#146;s actually proud off.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " oh! did you hear that?! my dad&#146;s proud of me! my dad&#146;s proud of me.", "answer": " rach?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " oh yeah, sorry. wait honey, so what did you do that made dad cut you off?", "answer": " okay, i bought a boat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " you bought a boat?", "answer": " yeah but it wasn&#146;t for me, it was for a friend.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " jill, honey, i think this is the best thing that could&#146;ve ever happened to you. i mean you needed to get out on your own anyway! and you know when i did it, i-i-i at first i was scared, and look at me now! i&#146;m the only daughter dad is proud of! okay, well this is, this is what you&#146;re gonna do. you&#146;re gonna get a job, you&#146;re gonna get an apartment, and then i&#146;ll help you and you can stay with us. right pheebs, she can stay with us?", "answer": " of course, yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " oh, that&#146;s so great! okay, i&#146;m really gonna do this! i don&#146;t know how to thank you guys.", "answer": " ooh, i like cards.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": "  are you all finished here?", "answer": " yes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " okay, here are the tips for this morning. jen gets 50, 50 for me, and joey owes eight dollars.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " for all the free food you gave away.", "answer": " well if it&#146;s free food, how come you&#146;re charging me for it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " we don&#146;t give anything away unless it&#146;s someone&#146;s birthday.", "answer": " well, what if they came in third in a modeling contest?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " no!", "answer": "  sorry!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " jill, how did you pay for all this? i thought your dad took away your credit card.", "answer": " oh please, i memorized those numbers when i was 15. but look at all the cool make-it-on-my-own stuff i got!  this is my &quot;please, hire me&quot; sweater.  and these are my, &quot;don&#146;t you want to rent me this apartment?&quot; pants.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " i don&#146;t think charging new clothes too your dad qualifies as making it on your own.", "answer": " oh, mr. scientist has to get all technical!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " seriously, i don&#146;t rachel&#146;s gonna think it&#146;s a good idea.", "answer": " so who made her queen of the world?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " i would love that job!", "answer": "  hey! what&#146;s goin&#146; on?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": "  jill! did you shop?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " no! they did!  phoebe and ross: yeah, we went shopping!", "answer": " you went shopping?! what, and then you just came in here and paraded it right under jill&#146;s nose when you know she&#146;s trying to quit. wow, you guys are terrible!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " sorry jill.", "answer": " sorry-sorry jill.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " what&#146;d you get?", "answer": " oh well, all right, i got   thank you, i got uh, this y&#146;know &quot;i want a job sweater.&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": " and, and then i got uh, these are apartment pants.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " apartment pants?", "answer": " yeah, you never heard of them?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " no, of course, of course i&#146;ve heard of them! ross, what did you get?", "answer": " huh? oh, i got this&#151;&#151;this!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " a pashmina?", "answer": " yeah! oh, i-i love this babies!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " ross, wants a pashmina?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " jill?", "answer": "  i&#146;m sorry rachel, i&#146;m sorry&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " oh, come on! you think that&#146;s gonna work on me?! i invented that!", "answer": " right! but, i am sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " she took all my stuff.", "answer": " yeah. everything but, the little blue one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": "  that&#146;s the best one! oh my god,  thank you so much!", "answer": " well. hey&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " oh my gosh, that was so lame. like a pashmina could be a rug!", "answer": " oh yeah, how about you and the,  &quot;i&#146;m sorry!&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": "  shut up! i did not sound like that at all!", "answer": " what about, what about when i said y&#146;know about the apartment pants, how dumb was i?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " were you this cute in high school?", "answer": " oh stop.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " no you stop!", "answer": " no, you stop!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " you stop!", "answer": "  okay-okay, why don&#146;t i sit here and you&#146;ll both stop it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " okay, so what do you, what do you want to do? let&#146;s do something crazy!", "answer": " i know, let&#146;s rest and drink lots of fluids.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " okay, i&#146;ll rest. but y&#146;know if i&#146;m going to bed, then you&#146;re coming with me.", "answer": " that would be impossible to resist if you weren&#146;t all drippy here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " yeah, i don&#146;t you should say that even when you&#146;re healthy.", "answer": "  come on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " don&#146;t take this personally okay? it&#146;s just that i just can&#146;t have sex with a sick person.", "answer": " i&#146;m with you chandler! i mean i can&#146;t have sex with a sick person either, that&#146;s disgusting! but i&#146;m not sick! let me prove it to you. we are two healthy people in the pribe of libe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " what&#146;s up?!", "answer": " umm, i think there&#146;s something you should maybe know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " well, it&#146;d better not be about the apartment pants, because i just pitched the idea to my boss at ralph lauren and she loved it.", "answer": " no. no. it&#146;s just i was umm, i was with ross and jill after you left and umm, i&#146;m pretty sure i saw a little spark between them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " yeah i mean it&#146;s probably nothing, but i just wanted to warn you that there might be something there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " with ross and jill?", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " with ross and my sister?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " with my sister jill and my ex-boyfriend ross?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " oh there is no way.", "answer": " okay then.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " oh my god! i can not believe that! i mean i don&#146;t really like it when ross goes out with anyone, but my sister isn&#146;t that like incest or something?! oh my god, and they&#146;re gonna have sex! oh! oh no what if he marries her too?! oh this is just terrible, this is just terrible. and i can&#146;t stop it! i can&#146;t&#151;i don&#146;t own ross! y&#146;know? and jill, she should be able to do whatever it is that she wants to do! and oh my god, i can&#146;t believe ross is marrying my little sister, this terrible. oh my god, this is just the worst thing that could have ever happened to", "answer": " but great news about the apartment pants, huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " that&#146;ll be $3.85.", "answer": " what do you mean? yesterday you said i was too pretty to pay for stuff!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " it&#146;s just i can&#146;t because my manager said i&#133;   &quot;happy birthday to you, happy birthday to you. happy birthday dear annie&#133;", "answer": " amy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": "  &quot;&#133;amy! happy birthday to you!&quot; a male customer: hey, that&#146;s weird, today&#146;s my birthday too!", "answer": " yeah, not it here it isn&#146;t.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": "  sorry i&#146;m late, what&#146;s up?", "answer": "  oh hi! y&#146;know, i just wanted to see if there were any leads on the old job front.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " oh no! but i just walked past three sales and i didn&#146;t go in. how strong am i?", "answer": " that is great. hey, y&#146;know who doesn&#146;t have to job hunt? ross. he works at the university.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " oh so you know that, you guys talked about that, so you get along, so you think you&#146;re gonna go out?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " me go out with ross?! no! god no! what would make you think that?", "answer": " i just, phoebe, said y&#146;know thought she saw something between you guys.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " no! i mean he&#146;s nice.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " he&#146;s the kind of guy you&#146;re friends with, y&#146;know? but he&#146;s not the kind of guy you date. he&#146;s the kind of guy you&#146;d date because you did. me, not so much.", "answer": " oh not-not so much. umm, what-what do you, what do you mean is there something wrong with ross?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " oh no-no-no, he&#146;s just i don&#146;t know, he&#146;s just a little bookish.", "answer": " are-are you saying he&#146;s a geek?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " you think so too?", "answer": " no! no i, no ross is not a geek!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " fine, then let&#146;s just say he&#146;s not my type.", "answer": " what handsome is not your type? smart? kind? good kisser? what those things aren&#146;t on your list? ross is a great guy! you would be lucky to be with him!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " well okay, if it means that much to you, then i&#146;ll ask him out.", "answer": " oh no-no-no, no-no-no, that&#146;s not what i meant.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " no! y&#146;know what rachel? you&#146;re right, y&#146;know he has been really nice to me.", "answer": " yeah but, he&#146;s not your type.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " yeah but maybe that&#146;s a good thing. y&#146;know i&#146;m doing all these different sorts of things, and maybe i should try dating a geek too!", "answer": " yeah but, you don&#146;t, you don&#146;t, you don&#146;t want to try to much too fast. y&#146;know? i mean, you do remember what happened to the little girl that tried to much too fast don&#146;t you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " she-she died jill. commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": "  chandler!", "answer": " oh what is it honey, you need some tea? some soup?  oh-ohhhh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": "  calling dr. big, dr. big to the bed.", "answer": " oh jeez honey, i thought, i thought you were asleep.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " how could i be asleep knowing that you were in the next room.", "answer": " i was asleep.  oh no! no-no honey! y&#146;know what&#146;s sexy? layers. layers are sexy. and blankets are sexy. and oh! hot water bottles are sexy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " would you please get some rest!", "answer": " i&#146;m fine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": "  &quot;happy birthday to you!&quot;", "answer": " you&#146;re paying for that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " what? no-no it&#146;s her birthday!", "answer": " you&#146;ve sung happy birthday to 20 different women today!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " but it really&#133;", "answer": " you are no longer authorized to distribute birthday muffins.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": "  rach? hi!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " did you tell your sister to ask me out?", "answer": " well yeah&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " oh wow! i mean, wow! i mean, i-i-i think she&#146;s cute but i-i would never have thought of going out with her, never!", "answer": " really?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " yeah but after you said it was okay, i figured, &quot;why not?!&quot;", "answer": " oh so-so not really never.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " i have to say you are a much bigger person than i am. i mean after all we&#146;ve been through, i just&#151;y&#146;know i wish i had a brother to reciprocate. hey, if you ever want to go out with monica, you have my blessing.", "answer": "  oh-ho, and mine!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": "  chandler, i think i&#146;m sick.", "answer": " really? struck down in the pribe of libe!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " no-no-no-no-no-no-no, you are not getting me this way.", "answer": " come on! i really need your help!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " no-no-no-no-no!", "answer": " fine, i&#146;ll rub it on myself.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " so you&#146;re just, kinda rubbing it on yourself?", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " it&#146;s nice.", "answer": " are you kidding me?! is this; is this turning you on?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " i can&#146;t believe it! what is it? is it the rubbing or the smell?", "answer": " it&#146;s all very, very good.  so you wanna go uh, mix it up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " not now, i&#146;m sick!", "answer": " oh come on you big faker!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " what happened to your rule about never sleeping with sick people?", "answer": " well that was before all the vaporizing action.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " okay, if you really wanna have sex&#133;", "answer": " okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": "  hi!", "answer": " hi! wh-what are you doing here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " well, i-i don&#146;t like it.", "answer": " really?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " it&#146;s kinda slutty.", "answer": " it&#146;s yours!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " yeah well, i&#146;m-i&#146;m a slut.", "answer": "  me too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": "  hi jill!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " hi .", "answer": " rachel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " rachel! well, you-you&#146;re not at home, you&#146;re-you&#146;re-you&#146;re right here.", "answer": " yeah i know, and i bet you thought it would be weird. but it&#146;s not!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " why aren&#146;t you home yet?!", "answer": "  is someone there?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " oh yes, it&#146;s me! sorry!", "answer": "  what are you doing here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " uh, i&#146;m just, i&#146;m just looking out your window. at-at the view. what are you guys doing?", "answer": " we got some vap-o-rub in some places.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": "  oh, he brought her back to his apartment.", "answer": "  who?  is that your sister?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " ugh, she is a slut!", "answer": " god, ross is on a date with your sister! how weird is that?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " oh my god, look-look he&#146;s taking off her clothes!", "answer": " he&#146;s taking off her coat!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " oh, this is just terrible.", "answer": " oh no it&#146;s not, no it&#146;s not. it&#146;s a first date. i&#146;m sure that nothing is gonna&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}]